{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Metal Awning Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40453/":{"taskOID":40453,"originalTaskOID":40453,"setID":744,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4575,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":915,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Awning is loose","answerDisplayText":"Awning is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Awning is bent or dented","answerDisplayText":"Awning is bent or dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Supporting bracket came loose or is broken","answerDisplayText":"Supporting bracket came loose or is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6201,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Support pole needs repair or replacing","answerDisplayText":"Support pole needs repair or replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4212,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"No longer retractable","answerDisplayText":"No longer retractable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5283,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Replace roofing panels","answerDisplayText":"Replace roofing panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":624,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Add electricity","answerDisplayText":"Add electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":637,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add new features","answerDisplayText":"Add new features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":652,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Add screens","answerDisplayText":"Add screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5723,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Awning/Patio Cover","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the awning or patio cover installed? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4575,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":915,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Awning is loose","answerDisplayText":"Awning is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Awning is bent or dented","answerDisplayText":"Awning is bent or dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Supporting bracket came loose or is broken","answerDisplayText":"Supporting bracket came loose or is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6201,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Support pole needs repair or replacing","answerDisplayText":"Support pole needs repair or replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4212,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"No longer retractable","answerDisplayText":"No longer retractable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5283,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Replace roofing panels","answerDisplayText":"Replace roofing panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":624,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Add electricity","answerDisplayText":"Add electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":637,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add new features","answerDisplayText":"Add new features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":652,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Add screens","answerDisplayText":"Add screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":915,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Awning is loose","answerDisplayText":"Awning is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Awning is bent or dented","answerDisplayText":"Awning is bent or dented","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Supporting bracket came loose or is broken","answerDisplayText":"Supporting bracket came loose or is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6201,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Support pole needs repair or replacing","answerDisplayText":"Support pole needs repair or replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4212,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"No longer retractable","answerDisplayText":"No longer retractable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5283,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Replace roofing panels","answerDisplayText":"Replace roofing panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":624,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Add electricity","answerDisplayText":"Add electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":637,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Add new features","answerDisplayText":"Add new features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":652,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Add screens","answerDisplayText":"Add screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5723,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Awning/Patio Cover","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the awning or patio cover installed? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7005,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window(s)","answerDisplayText":"Window(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2033,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4807,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Porch","answerDisplayText":"Porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40453/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40453,"taskName":"Metal Awning or Patio Cover - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Metal Awnings or Patio Covers","xmTaskDescriptor":"Metal Awning Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":17,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Metal window retractable covers porch","textMessagingName":"Repr Metal Awn","rolloverLongDesc":"Awnings provide shade to exterior spaces as well as prevent hot summer sunshine from heating interior spaces \u0026 fading fabrics. Many metal units use a slat design to provide shade in summer \u0026 allow sunlight to penetrate in winter when the angle of the sun is lower. Note separate categories for metal awning repairs, fabric awnings, shutters \u0026 window tinting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair motors or replace bent or missing parts","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Metal Awnings or Patio Covers.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Metal Awning Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Metal Patio Cover Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":7,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Metal Awning or Patio Cover Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Metal Awning or Patio Cover - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Metal Awning and Patio Cover Project","urlName":"Metal-Awning-or-Patio-Cover-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Metal Awning/Patio Cover Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"metal awning, porch, awning, retractable awning, retractable, porch cover, metal","emcCategoryOid":-12007,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":744,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}